干洗店
The dry cleaning,
面包店  全部生意
the bakeries, the everything.
这也是一个机会
There's also an opportunity here.
我明白  我跟他略提了一下
I know. I sowed some seeds.
他的合法生意带来了什么好处
His legitimate business brings in what?
给我们每年500万的收入?
Five million a year to us?
毒品买卖能挣2000万  甚至更多
Drug business brings in 20. Maybe more.
我还以为我们想避免涉及毒品案件
I thought we wanted to stay away from drugs.
那是理想状态
Ideally.
我们正处在艰难时期
But we're in a tough time.
若我们不抢卡特·帕拉迪尼的活儿
If we don't go after Cutner & Paradini's business,
-他们就会来抢我们的  -好吧
- they'll come after ours. - Okay.
保持联络
We'll stay in touch.
潜在客户?
A possible client?
是的
Yes.
一个大毒枭
A drug dealer.
在此之前我们一直抗拒他的非法生意
We've always resisted his illegal business until now.
-为什么  -毒品案件很棘手
- Why? - Drugs are tricky.
更引公众瞩目
You're more in the public eye.